AXEL SANTO DOMINGO

AUDIO ENGINEER / RECORDING ARTIST

23 year-old audio engineer and recording artist specializing in R&B and hip-hop located in the Greater Twin Cities. Establishing member of the MARAJ LLC music collective. Forte in writing choruses and original melodies. Seasoned photographer and social media manager.

axelsantodomingo.com axelsantodomingo@gmail.com +17632918625

EXPERIENCE

Audio Engineer

Freelance / 2013 - Present theMARAJ / 2015 - Present

Worked with established national and local artists in recording, editing, and mixing vocals and instrumentals.

Recording Artist

theMARAJ / 2011 - Present

Composed original music in any of the following genres: R&B, hip-hop, rap, EDM, dancehall, pop, funk, soul, alternative, reggaeton. Featured on collaborative tracks with local artists.

Social Media Manager

theMARAJ / 2018 - Present

Increased audience interaction with Instagram posts by over 3000% within a week for "Dripstars" album release by creating social media video content.

TECHNICAL SKILLS

Logic Pro X

8 years' professional experience

Adobe Premiere

3 years' academic experience

EDUCATION

University of Minnesota

Twin Cities Campus / 2018 - Present BA in Cinema and Media Culture Minor in Digital Media

Normandale Community College

Bloomington, MN / 2016 - 2018

References available upon request